<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="webinterface.tofu"
  version="0.1.1"
  name="TOFU"
  provider-name="Pivos Technology Group">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.webinterface"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">(TOFU se verstek web koppelvlak)</summary>
    <summary lang="am_ET">(የ TOFU ነባር የዌብ ገጽታዎች)</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA"> (واجهه الشبكة العنكبوتية المبدئية لـ توفو)</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">(TOFU's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">(стандартният уеб интерфейс на TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">(Interficie web per defecte del TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">(Výchozí webové rozhraní TOFU).</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">(Rhyngwyneb gwe rhagosodedig TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">(TOFU's standard webgrænseflade)</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">(Standardwebinterface von TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">(Προεπιλεγμένη διεπαφή ιστού του TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">(TOFU's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">(TOFU's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">(TOFU's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">(TOFU's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">(Interfaz web por defecto de TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">(Interfaz web por defecto de TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">(Interfaz Web por defecto de TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">(Vaikimisi keskkond)</summary>
    <summary lang="eu_ES">(TOFU-ren lehenetsiriko web interfazea)</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_AF">(رابط پیش فرض TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_IR">(رابط وب استاندارد TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">(TOFU:n oletus WWW-käyttöliittymä)</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">(Interface Web par défaut d'TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">(Interface Web prédéfinie de TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">(Interface web predefinida de TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">(ברירת המחדל)</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">(TOFUjevo uobičajeno web sučelje)</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">(TOFU alapértelmezett webes kezelőfelülete)</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">(Antar muka web bawaan TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">(Sjálfgefið vefviðmót á TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">(Interfaccia web di default per TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">(TOFU's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">(TOFU 기본 웹 인터페이스)</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">(TOFU numatytoji žiniatinklio sąsaja)</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">(TOFU noklusētā tīmekļa saskarne)</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">(TOFU's подразбирачки веб интерфејс)</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">(antaramuka web lalai TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="my_MM">(TOFU ၏ မူရင် ဝက်ဘ် အသွင်အပြင်)</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">(TOFUs standard nettgrensesnitt)</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">(TOFU's standaard webinterface)</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">(Domyślny)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">(interface web padrão do TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">(Interface web predefinida do TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">(interfață web implicită pentru TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">(веб-интерфейс TOFU по умолчанию).</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">(predvolené webové rozhranie pre TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">(Privzet spletni vmesnik za TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS">(подразумевани веб интерфејс TOFU-а)</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS@latin">(подразумевани веб интерфејс TOFU-а)</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">(TOFU's standardwebbgränssnitt)</summary>
    <summary lang="szl">(wychodny webowy interface we TOFU).</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">(கோடியின் நிரந்தர இணைய இடைமுகம்)</summary>
    <summary lang="te_IN">(కోడి యొక్క డిఫాల్ట్ వెబ్ ఇంటర్ఫేస్)</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">(Интерфейси веби пешфарз барои TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">(ส่วนประสานหน้าเว็บพื้นฐานของ TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">(TOFU'nin varsayılan web arayüzü)</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">(Типовий веб-інтерфейс  для TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="uz_UZ">(TOFU andoza veb interfeysi)</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">(Giao diện Web mặc định của TOFU)</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">（TOFU 的默认 web 界面）</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">(TOFU的預設網頁介面)</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Verstek web koppelvlak vir TOFU; Ontwerp vir toestelle van alle resolusies (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="am_ET">ነባር የዌብ ገጽታዎች ለ TOFU ፡ የተነደፈው ለሁሉም አካላቶች resolutions ነው  (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">واجهه الشبكة العنكبوتية المبدئية لـ توفو، مُصمَمة لتناسب كافة قياسات أبعاد الشاشات (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">Стандартны вэб-інтэрфэйс да TOFU; распрацаваны для прыладаў зь любымі разрознасьцямі (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Стандартния уеб интерфейс на TOFU; Направен е за устройства с най-различни резолюции (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Interfície web per defecte del TOFU; Dissenyada per dispositius de totes les resol·lucions (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Výchozí webové rozhraní TOFU navržené pro zařízení s libovolným rozlišením (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Rhyngwyneb gwe rhagosodedig TOFU. Wedi ei gynllunio ar gyfer cydraniad pob dyfais (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Standard webgrænseflade til TOFU; designet til enheder i alle opløsninger (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Standard TOFU Webinterface - Für alle Geräte und Auflösungen geeignet (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Προεπιλεγμένη διεπαφή ιστού για το TOFU. Σχεδιασμένη για συσκευές όλων των αναλύσεων. (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Default web interface for TOFU; Designed for devices of all resolutions (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">Default web interface for TOFU; Designed for devices of all resolutions (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Default web interface for TOFU; Designed for devices of all resolutions (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Default web interface for TOFU; Designed for devices of all resolutions (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Interfaz web por defecto de TOFU. Diseñada para dispositivos de cualquier resolución (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Interfaz web por defecto de TOFU. Diseñada para dispositivos de cualquier resolución (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Interfaz Web por defecto para TOFU; Diseñado para dispositivos de todas las resoluciones (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">TOFU vaikimisi veebikeskkond; Disainitud erinevate resolutsioonidega seadmetele. (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="eu_ES">TOFU-ren lehenetsiriko web interfazea. Erresoluzio guztietako gailentzat diseinatua (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="fa_AF">رابط پیش فرض TOFUوطراحی شده برای هر رزولیشن (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="fa_IR">رابط استاندارد وب برای TOFU. قابل استفاده برای همه دستگاه ها و همه رزولوشن ها (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Oletus WWW-käyttöliittymä TOFU:lle. Suunniteltu käytettäväksi kaiken kokoisilla laitteilla. (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Interface Web par défaut d'TOFU - Conçue pour les dispositifs de toutes résolutions (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Interface Web prédéfini de TOFU ; adaptée aux appareils de toutes résolutions (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Interface web predefinida para TOFU, deseñada para dispositivos de todas as resolucións (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">ממשק דפדפן ברירת המחדל עבור TOFU; מותאם למכשירים בעלי אבחנות שונות (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Uobičajeno web sučelje za TOFU; Dizajnirano za uređaje svih razlučivosti (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Az TOFU alapértelmezett webes kezelőfelülete; Minden felbontásra alkalmas (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="hy_AM">Նախնական տեսք TOFU-ի համար; Նախատեսված է բոլոր կրիչների համար (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Antar muka web bawaan bagi TOFU; Dirancang bagi perangkat dengan semua resolusi (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Sjálfgefið vefviðmót fyrir TOFU; Hannað fyrir tæki með allskonar upplausnir (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Interfaccia Web di default per TOFU; Realizzata per periferiche con qualunque risoluzione (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">TOFU のデフォルト Web インターフェースです。さまざまな解像度のデバイス用にデザインされています。 (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">TOFU 기본 웹 인터페이스; 모든 해상도의 기기를 위해 디자인 됨 (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Numatytoji TOFU Web sąsaja skirta visų rezoliucijų prietaisams (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Noklusētā TOFU tīmekļa sakarne; Piemērota visu izšķirtspēju iekārtām (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">Подразбирачки веб интерфејс за TOFU; Дизајниран за уреди со сите резолуции (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Antaramuka web lalai untuk TOFU; Di reka untuk peranti pelbagai resolusi (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="my_MM">TOFU အတွက် မူရင်း ဝက်ဘ် အသွင်ပြင် ၊ စက်များ အားလုံး၏ resolutions အတွက် ရေးဆွဲထားသည်။ (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Standard nettgrensesnitt for TOFU; Laget for alle oppløsninger (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Standaard TOFU-webinterface; geschikt voor alle resoluties (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Domyślny interfejs webowy TOFU; Zaprojektowany dla urządzeń o ekranach w dowolnej rozdzielczości (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Interface web padrão para TOFU; Concebida para dispositivos de todas as resoluções (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Interface web predefinida do TOFU. Concebida para dispositivos de todas as resoluções (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Interfață web implicită pentru TOFU, realizată de echipa TOFU pentru dispozitive cu orice rezoluție. (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Веб-интерфейс TOFU по умолчанию. Разработан для устройств с любыми разрешениями. (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="si_LK">TOFU' සඳහා නියත  වෙබ් අතුරුමුහුණත; සෑම විභේදනයකම උපකරණ සඳහා නිර්මාණය කර ඇත (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Predvolené webové rozhranie pre TOFU; Navrhnuté pre zariadenia zobrazujúce v akomkoľvek rozlíšení (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Privzet spletni vmesnik za TOFU, ustvarjen za naprave vseh ločljivosti (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS">Подразумевани веб интерфејс TOFU-а, намењен уређајима свих резолуција (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS@latin">Подразумевани веб интерфејс TOFU-а, намењен уређајима свих резолуција (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Standardwebbgränssnitt för TOFU; Utformat för alla enheter oavsett skärmupplösning (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="szl">Wychodny webowy interface we TOFU. Zrychtowany dlŏ maszin we wszyjskich rozdziylczościach. (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">கோடி இற்கான நிரந்தர இணைய இடைமுகம்; சகல சாதனங்களின் திரைகளுக்கும் வடிவமைக்கப்பட்டது (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="te_IN">కోడి డిఫాల్ట్ వెబ్ ఇంటర్ఫేస్; అన్ని వైశాల్యాలు పరికరాల కోసం రూపొందించబడింది (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">Интерфейси веби пешфарз барои TOFU; Барои ҳар гуна дастгоҳ бо возеҳии экранаш гуногун эҷод карда шудааст (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">ส่วนประสานหน้าเว็บพื้นฐานสำหรับ TOFU ได้ออกแบบรองรับความละเอียดหน้าจอของอุปกรณ์ทั้งหมด (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">TOFU için varsayılan web arayüzü; Bütün çözünürlüklerde tüm cihazlar için dizayn edilmiştir. (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Типовий веб-інтерфейс  для TOFU; Розроблений для пристроїв з будь-якою роздільною здатністю (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="uz_UZ">TOFU uchun andoza veb interfeysi; barcha ekran o'lchamlari bilan uskunalar uchun yaratilgan (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Web mặc định cho TOFU; Thiết kế cho các thiết bị ở tất cả độ phân giải khác nhau (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">TOFU 的默认 web 界面；为支持所有分辨率的设备而设计 (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">TOFU的預設網頁介面；針對所有解析度的設備而設計 (Base: Team-Kodi Default web interface)</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
